kaki narase sonzai wo
rock away your existence
koko ni iru to
shouting that you are here
arata na tabi ga ima hajimaru
a new journey begins now
kawari yuku kisetsu no naka wo ikinuku tabi ni bokura
as we survived through the changing seasons
chie to tsuyosa wo te ni ireta kedo JUST LOOKS LIKE SURVIVAL GAME
we gained knowledge and strength (just looks like a survival game)
nagareteku jikan no naka ni
but the forgotten memories
okizari ni shita omoi wo
of the feelings abandoned within the flows of time
wasureta koto sura wasurete ita
have also been lost
kuzure kaketa toki kodoku wo shitte
when sinking down we learned loneliness
deaeta bokura hitori ja nai
but now we've met each other we are no longer alone
sarake dase kanjou wo banjou no omoi wo
unveil your feelings those high emotions
namidame ga unmei wo kaete yuku
those tears will change your fate
yami ni uchi narase kodou wo
pound your heartbeat against the darkness
kitto aeru yo onaji itami no hata no moto de
we're sure to meet under the same flag of pain
I'll give it to you straight.
Your next mission was commissioned
by a certain feudal lord's daughter.
You are to act as her double.
I don't know where she heard about you,
but you apparently bear
a striking resemblance to the princess.
Therefore she requested
that you be the one who carries it out.
A double?
Is someone targeting the princess?
Well, if anything,
she's the one who's doing the targeting.
Not to worry.
You're already
an admirable Hidden Leaf Shinobi.
Furthermore, I've arranged
for you to have an assistant.
Assistant?
Grandma Tsunade!
You have a mission for me?
And one from a feudal lord to boot!
Huh?! Tsunade-sama!
Sorry,
but all the other guys are too busy.
Just me and this guy?
Yes. Do your best
to carry out the mission.
The client is
a feudal lord's daughter, huh?
Wow. I guess that means
that I've finally become good enough
to handle amazing missions
like this, huh?!
Hey, don't get too excited.
Terrible things happen
when you're like that.
I know...
Just leave things in my capable hands!
You're a real piece of work.
Ino Screams! Chubby ♥ Paradise
Thank you for coming from afar.
That's the client?
She and Ino really do look alike, but...
It's a bit of a stretch.
It's all right.
I have an idea of what you wish to say.
My physique doesn't really resemble
that of the double there.
That's what you're thinking, right?
— Oh, not at all. Um...
— To be honest,
— I don't think you resemble her at all.
— Hey!
Well, I don't blame you for thinking that.
But here, have a look at this!
That's Ino!
That's what I looked like
a short time ago.
Truth be told, I only got like this
after it was decided that I was
to have an arranged courtship.
An arranged courtship?!
The other party is Master Chikara
from the neighbouring Land of Udon.
Ever since I saw his picture,
my feelings for him have
deepened day by day.
And as the day
of the arranged courtship grows closer,
I have become increasingly nervous,
my cheeks have been flushed,
and my heart has been pounding.
I can't even sleep at night.
And because of that stress,
I've started overeating.
It goes without saying
that you'll get fat if you pig out.
Of course,
I've taken appropriate countermeasures!
I've been using something that cuts all
the fats and carbohydrates that I ingest.
"EASY-PEASY SLIM SPECIAL"
It didn't work, did it?
I placed too strong hopes in it.
How can I possibly have
an arranged courtship
with the man I'm infatuated with
when I look like this?
So, that's my situation.
Now, let's get to the main issue.
I want you to attend
the arranged courtship in my place
and make it a success at any cost.
Huh?! So, this double thing
is just to act on you behalf
at some arranged courtship?!
What do you mean
by "some arranged courtship"?!
I mean, when you talk about doubles,
you think of situations
where someone's life is in danger
and that sort of thing.
What are you talking about?!
The princess's entire life is at stake!
This is major!
Oh! So, you understand a heart in love.
I sure do.
A girl always wants to look cute
for the guy she loves.
Even if she's a fake?
It can't be helped.
I mean, guys prefer slender girls.
That's exactly right!
I'm counting on you.
Sure thing! Leave it to me!
But even if
the arranged courtship goes well,
the gap is just too big.
I'll just have to lose weight
by the day of the wedding.
I already have a plan in place for that.
This supplemental type diet food,
"Supplement Slender"!
If I supplement all three meals
with this...
Why don't you draw on the lessons
you're supposed to have learned?
In any case, I'll use my charms to make
this arranged courtship a success!
This annex is where
I often played in my childhood.
I plan to use this to listen in on
the arranged courtship from here.
That's pretty convenient.
I would love to meet him in person
if I could, but...
Hey, is he that cool-looking?
Of course he is!
He's someone
with something really special about him!
Well, then, just make sure
he falls for you.
Leave it to me!
I thought you weren't motivated.
Well, this is a mission after all.
So, I think I'll pull myself together
and hustle!
Don't do anything unnecessary, okay?
What's up?
The sound is getting closer!
— What?
— It's so bright!
There are many a handsome man
in this world,
but this man is renowned
even among them!
This man makes Land of Udon what it is...
that sexy man
with glistening sidelong glances!
The oh-so-great young prince Chikara.
Kneel down and bow before him!
Sorry.
It appears
that I have kept you waiting, princess.
You're... Master Chikara?
He's even more intense
than Intense-Brow Sensei.
I'm sorry, pretty girl.
I have constitutional low blood pressure.
I don't know. He looks more like
he has high blood pressure to me.
What?
Do you always scatter flower petals?
Flowers are wonderful.
They truly allay the fatigue
of your mind and body.
Don't you find them relaxing?
I guess.
Okay, then, next.
Hey, don't you think
he's different from her description?
— I mean, he's fa...
— Fa...?!
Stop!
These sweets are really fabulous,
aren't they?
Do excuse us.
What the heck are you doing,
out of the blue like that?!
It's women's intuition.
I got the same vibe from him as Choji.
That word is probably taboo.
Oh, I see!
Give me a break!
What's up with that uselessly
intense chubby guy showing up
when she told us
he'd be a handsome prince?!
But wouldn't his physique be
a perfect match for her?
I'm sure there must be some mistake.
There's no way a girl would fall in love
with a guy like that.
But maybe that's
the princess's taste in men.
That's impossible. I mean...
He's flashy! Intense! And a fatso!
He's a freak! A freak!
There's gotta be a mistake!
I'm sure of it!
You think so?
What are you saying?
There's no mistake that that's
Master Chikara, the man of my heart.
I thought so.
What an elegant man.
I deeply regret that I cannot see him
up close with my very own eyes.
I guess one could say
that everybody has their own set of woes.
Listen, make sure that he takes
a liking to me, no matter what!
Stop complaining and get the ball rolling
with dogged persistence!
I will convey that to her.
Has your tension not eased?
Music is good for relaxation.
Please, you need not go to the trouble.
— What did she say?
— She said there's no mistake.
She wants you to bulldoze on ahead!
I can't believe it!
It's our mission, you know!
I know that.
Princess Fuku, do you like roses?
Yes, very much so.
Great! I love roses, too!
In the language of flowers,
they signify love!
But don't their meanings differ
depending on their color?
For example, yellow roses are supposed
to mean "let's break up."
It's nonsense to discriminate
because of color.
I mean,
the flowers are not at fault, after all.
For you.
Hey... wait!
Huh?
I can't do it! I can't do it!
There's no way! He's too intense.
There's no way I can act
as a substitute for the princess!
Calm down.
Stop saying that and do your best.
Nope. I just can't stand him physically.
Oh, I got it.
If you just think of him
— as a somewhat intense Choji...
— Choji has fat on him
for the sake of his Ninjutsu.
I don't have the slightest idea
what purpose that prince's fat serves.
That's a pretty severe opinion,
you know?
I need to get away for a moment.
Huh? Hey, where are you going?
Give me a break, that girl's a handful...
Well, this is for the sake
of a mission after all.
I guess it's about time
for Naruto to lend a helping hand!
What is it?!
I'm not judging you, but I think you
should pass on that young prince.
There's something wrong with his head.
I'm positive!
What are you saying?
He's a passionate and wonderful man!
But...
I hired the Leaf to provide me
with a substitute
for the arranged courtship
and bring it to success.
You're a professional Shinobi, right?
So, I suggest you get on it
and get the job done!
The atmosphere in there hasn't been
very congenial at all!
You need to be aggressive
in making yourself appealing to him!
I'm sorry
to have kept you waiting, Chikara!
That's right! Just like that... Huh?
— That jerk!
— Hey!
Princess?
Master Chikara, could you loosen
my sash for me, please?
But... But...
Please.
Oh, my gosh!
There's a creepy-crawler up here
under the roof that looks like a sow bug!
Mind Destruction Jutsu!
A creepy-crawler
that looks like a sow bug?
An insect?
Oh, she vanished.
What the heck are you thinking?!
— Where is the princess?!
— I don't know!
She vanished.
What is going on?
This is starting to irritate me.
I can't get what's happening from here.
Why are you meddling!
I was just one step away!
What do you think you're doing,
dressed up like Princess Fuku?!
I'm telling you!
In one of Pervy Sage's books
I glanced at,
this is the kind of thing that worked.
I don't believe that anyone would
use such a garish advance!
That's dirty!
There's absolutely no way
a type of guy like you
would ever be mistaken
for the protagonist of a shounen manga!
Huh! I was doing a way better job
than you were!
Give me a break.
Now that things have come to this,
I need to take care of business
before another meddler gets in the way.
Huh. You gotta be kidding.
It looks like my help is needed
if this mission is going to succeed.
Princess, where in the world
have you been?
Please forgive me. I was so nervous,
I flew into a panic earlier on.
You really seemed like
a totally different person.
I'm so sorry.
You were such a wonderful person,
that it became almost unbearable.
No. That is bad.
We must change the air in here, then.
Oh, in that case, I will.
Hi, Chikara!
That just now,
outside the paper door...
What's the matter?
There was another princess!
That can't be. Impossible.
"INFERNO"
Naruto!
But I'm very moved that
you have such deep feelings for me
that you actually saw a vision.
Vision? No, I definitely saw...
You mustn't look!
Princess?
Damn. I did that without thinking.
Oh, goodness me.
In my ardent desire for you
to look just at me, I...
What intense passion.
All right. As you wish, princess.
Allow me to catch
those hot feelings in fine style.
Could this be...?
Come, don't hold back.
You may not kiss him! No kisses!
Goodness, you cannot be
too careful these days!
Who told you that you could go
as far as to kiss him?!
Oh, it's not that I wanted to...
I'd have to say
that you actually came to my rescue.
Don't bandy words with me!
Listen carefully, holding hands is
as much as I can concede to you...!
You're too loud.
The princess vanished again.
— Princess!
This isn't good! I'd better hurry back.
Don't try anything funny in there!
I know that! In any case, we can't let him
see the two of us together!
Hurry back to your room, princess!
All right.
Give me a break. That Ino...
Dumping me in the lake like that.
Thanks to her, I'm freezing!
This is bad! I gotta pee. Gotta go!
I don't know
where the toilet is around here.
There's nobody around.
It is an emergency situation after all.
Huh?!
What the heck do you think
you're doing over there looking like me?!
No, this is... Um...
How shameless!
Stop that immediately!
I can't stop it!
Do you not understand
that I'm telling you to stop!
It's impossible to stop so suddenly!
Hey!
Wait up!
I wasn't quite
emotionally prepared earlier on.
However, the feelings I have
for you in my heart are true.
Princess...
Master Chikara,
I have harbored a secret love for you
for a long time.
Please, take me.
Huh?
— I wonder what that sound is.
— I have no idea.
Rain?
What a beautiful rainbow.
Stop, I say!
I told you, it's impossible!
— Ouch!
— Princess?!
Naruto!
You idiot!
Forgive me for this one, please!
I won't forgive you!
Look what you've done!
Ouch! Stop!
What in the world is going on?
Oh, no! Um... This is, well...
All right, that's enough.
We can't fake it any longer.
I apologize for having hoodwinked you.
I am the bona fide Fuku.
You mean to say that the princess
up to now was an imposter?
That is correct.
What is the meaning of all this?
I wouldn't have imagined
that things would come to such a finale!
No, that's not correct, Master Chikara!
Out of my way!
The super body I fantasized about
in my dreams! My ideal personified!
Bravo!
My cute princess. Please marry me!
I'm delighted, Master Chikara!
Hail the future wife!
What is this anyway?
Somehow it seems like our mission
turned out to be success in the end.
I think?
Could it be? I put all my efforts
in making advances on a guy
who's not my type in the least
and got rejected.
Moreover,
it was a completely wasted effort.
Is that what happened?
But everything turned out well.
So, isn't it okay?
And both of them looked so happy together.
That's not the problem!
A damsel's heart has been wounded.
I can't believe that, of all things,
I was brushed off by a guy like that.
He didn't even glance in your direction
at the end there.
Stop it! Don't remind me.
You can never know
what a person likes, can you?
Nope. There's no way
I'll acknowledge that!
A man's got to like a slender girl better!
In order to become
even more of a woman,
I'm going on a diet! On a diet!
Wait! Wait up!
hoshikuzu suchasucha sucha odoru
on a checkerboard night
ichimatsu no yoru ni
when the stardust's are rapidly dancing
aa mada kaeri takunai to kuchi ni wa dasenai naa
I just can't come out and say, "ah, I don't want to go home yet"
omowa seburi terii
suggestively
aisubeki kao ni tsuba wo misutaa kuriketto
spat at that beloved face, mister cricket
asekusai suteeji no ue de hikaru toronboon no
the trombone gradually going off-key
picchi ga dandan hazureteitteiru no mo kininaru kedo
while on the sweaty center stage does bug me
sonna koto yori kono nai mune no moyamoya wa sakki
but more importantly, the fuzziness I feel in my undeveloped chest,
nonda koora no sei kashira nee
I wonder If it's from that coke I just drank?
Naruto, let's make some
bittersweet memories of youth together!
— Huh?
— No need to be shy.
I am ready both in mind and body!
What are you blabbing about
all of a sudden?!
It was long...
To think how much
I've waited for this moment!
I have no idea what you're talking about!
Here I come Naruto!
Please become my first.
Just a minute.
Next Time:
"Viva Dojo Challenge! Explosion of Youth."